All right. So, uh, started the day with,
uh, four picks in five. Had to wait a
little bit. Um, took some patience, but
really happy with how it played out. Um,
you know, we took Parker Braillesford,
made one trade with Seattle to pick up a
future four. Um, took Justin Jefferson
out of Alabama, and then made another
trade back in five to also pick up a
future six. So, the whole net, really
pleased with that. um can certainly open
up to questions on both Parker and
Justin um as you have them.
>> So Parker's like under 300 pounds, which
is becoming an unusual for a center. Was
that the physical set you were looking
for there?
>> A lighter center.
>> Light I wouldn't say that. I think an
athletic center. What he does really
well is move in the run game. Got uh
tremendous range. Um, great finish. To
be honest, if you didn't know his
measurables on his card, you wouldn't
say he plays like a sub 300 pound
player. He's strong, firm. Um, so really
like the skill set and really like how
it fits with uh the offensive scheme.
>> Along those lines, I was going to say
like what you what you just described,
it seems like it maybe the the frame is
similar to Tyler Lander and Mon being
there. Was that something that you saw
parallels to or was it kind of a
different type of player?
>> Yeah, I you don't want to directly
compare him one to one with, you know,
Linder Bond, but I would say that you
have seen coach Monkin play with an
athletic center with range and do a lot
of creative stuff in the run game and
that certainly is appealing in terms of
Parker and how we would deploy him.
>> Long saw the fastest 10 yard split of
any other line at the combine. How
important are those movement skills,
especially for what you guys?
>> Yeah, really important. I mean, the main
thing that they got to do is get on guys
and get on guys quickly. And so, the
guys with range who can climb to the
second level, pull, move out in space,
you know, all of that's predicated on
having quickness, athleticism, and
range. So, guys who can move like that
are, you know, are really successful in
the scheme. when you're looking on day
three, how much that, you know, both
these guys come from a program at
Alabama. How much do you kind of look at
the pedigree of the where where they
come from, you know, in terms of hoping
to catch guys maybe develop maybe a
little further along or in the
development for this net to jump to the
next level?
>> Yeah. You know, I would say the
interesting thing with both of them is
they didn't start their careers at
Alabama, right? So Parker starts off at
Washington, transfers to Alabama. Justin
started off in JO, transferred to
Alabama. Um, both those guys had a like
a developmental curve. Uh, and with
Parker in particular, you know, I think
it's he's playing against the best of
the best in the SEC. So, he is matching
up against guys with size who he's going
to have to face in the NFL. And and that
is something that maybe if you have a
small school guy who lacks size, you're
making more of a projection on how
that'll play out. Justin, what did you
guys like about him and and what do you
kind of envision him adding to that
linebacker room? And it looks like maybe
on special teams, too.
>> Yeah, really nice scheme fit first and
foremost. I mean, we have played with um
you know, Devin Bush, we signed Quincy
Williams. Both of those guys are around
the same size, six foot, really fast,
really athletic. So, just a real clean
and vision for how he fits into the
scheme. Um, and then when you have guys
who can run 44, um, and like to hit,
that translates pretty well on special
teams. So, I think, you know, Justin,
both on defense and on special teams
will have a nice role.
>> With the four fifth round picks, was
there any effort to move up in the
round?
>> That's something we discussed. Yeah. And
discussed moving up. Obviously, we moved
back, you know, with one of the picks
and we moved out entirely with one of
the picks. So
>> state center went a few notches ahead of
your center
>> there. There was there was a run on the
centers, but to be honest, Parker was
the guy we had targeted all along.
>> Can he get bigger or is this his 289? Is
that his size?
>> He played in the high 280s, you know,
low 290s. I I think he is more than
capable at functioning and playing where
he's at in terms of his weight.
Obviously, you guys have devoted a bunch
of resources to the offensive line in
the last month and a half. Coming into
the draft, how important or how much of
a focus was it to add somebody at that
center spot?
>> I wouldn't say there was a focus at one
particular spot. I think the focus was
adding good players along the offensive
line. Um, I think it's been noted we've
added guys with positional versatility.
That's important. We know that you're
going into the year you're going to have
your starting five, but the reality is
you're going to play with more than
five. I think last year the top if you
played more than 50% of your snaps with
your top five linemen, you would have
been in the top 10 in the league. So,
you're going to have to cover, you know,
a,000 2,000 snaps somewhere on the line
with other guys usually the way injuries
go. So, you know, I think we just were
focused on getting good players who
could play on the line and then, you
know, figuring out the configuration
from there. Dan, do you think um are
some positions
uh easier for guys drafted later to
succeed than others such as Don Parker
here in in this round?
>> I think there are certain positions
within certain schemes that you might
anticipate a quicker transition, you
know, going from college to pro. Uh but
I do think it's it's across schemes more
than maybe necessarily across positions.
You saw Andrew trade out of the third
round then back in. Is Is that kind of
what he's doing with this trade
down to the sixth round?
>> Is he going back up or I don't see the
logic in that?
>> No, I think we just got, you know, a
really good offer to to draw it back in
five and still pick up a an extra pick,
you know, nearby. So 170 and 182. Um
with you know feel pretty confident that
the same kind of set of players that we
would consider there will be available
you know a few few slots later.